

Summary

San Francisco based UX designer utilizing my past experiences and newly developed design skills to produce data-driven functionality and aesthetically pleasing solutions.

Recent Projects

Fruition Brewing | Web page design and development of breweries website

- UX, Research, Information architecture, Development (HTML CSS and JavaScript)
- Link to Case Study (website in development)

Newlocal | location based iOS application design prototyping and testing

- Lead designer, UX, Branding, Research, Information architecture, Prototype and Testing
- Link to InVision prototype; link to Case Study

Experience

Uber ATG | Engineering Operations Technician Aug. 2016 - Present

- Documented and implemented procedures to convert an OEM semi-truck into an autonomous semi-truck.
- Data analysis and platform triage for Uber's autonomous trucks program

Ottomotto LLC. (acquired by Uber Aug. 2016) | Engineering Operations Technician | Feb. 2017 - Aug. 2018

- Assisted with truck retrofit and helped develop a truck build inventory system using QR codes
- Managed a small team that collected, annotated and QC'd images for our perception system.
- Analyzed potential acquisition of company that would be able to replace our labeling workforce/needs.

Google Inc. | Program Manager - Engineering Operations (Self-Driving Cars) | June 2012 - Dec. 2015

- Worked cross-functionally with multiple teams to coordinate and manage the logistics and the documentation of various tests for on-board engineering, systems engineering, mechanical engineering, UX, public relations/marketing, and business development.
- Helped run and develop procedures for conducting UX studies for various aspects of the self-driving car.
- Played a key role in managing and growing our operations team, including the hiring and training of over 100 contractors, while maintaining the highest level of safety.

nicolasmunley.com (415) 810 - 3223 nrmunley@gmail.com

Skills

Visual Design
UX/UI Design
Project Management
User Research & Testing
Brand Strategy & Identity
Information Architecture
Personas & User Stories
Wireframing & Prototyping
Agile and Scrum

Programming Skills

Working Knowledge

HTML

CSS

Basic Knowledge

JavaScript

SQL

Linux

CSS Grid

Tools

Adobe Creative Suite

Sketch

Figma

InVision

Usability Hub

GitHub

Maze

Typeform

Marvel App

Education

Bloc | UX/UI Design and Development Apprenticeship |

Feb. 2017 - Aug. 2018

CSU Chico | BS Civil Engineering | Aug. 2005 - May. 2010





